Darling, Darling
Sailing
on the cobalt
blue The clouds float above the sea
Hanging out just
me and you Our
time is now and soon you'll see
smile with all your heart
as you go past the problems
that await you keep your
hopes alive never look
down upon yourself just
cast a magic spell you will
get through crazy crazy
rainbow star twinkle twinkle
rainbow star fast beats
premonitions just like the
colors from all the rainbow
beams crazy crazy rainbow
star come with me and
we'll go far we're just
fallen angels shooting arrows
into our hopeful dreams
crazy crazy rainbow star
i'm a crazy rainbow star
Crazy, crazy rainbow star Twinkle,
twinkle rainbow star
Within the cobalt blue
Seven colors will come
to our surprise Crazy,
crazy rainbow star Twinkle,
twinkle rainbow star Abandon
all your worries Your troubles
show through the mirror of
your eyes Let me comfort you,
my love I'll hold your time
within my glove We sure are fallen
angels Just singing our hearts
All out from up above Dying,
dying Crazy, crazy hippo star
I'm a crazy hippo star Crazy,
crazy hippo star I'm a crazy hippo star
So Usopp's really gonna come back?
Uh-huh.
I saw him on the coast.
He was practicing his big return speech.
That's great news!
Man, I was so worried!
Okay, let's go get him right now!
Well, that's Usopp for you.
Should have known.
We're gonna get our crew back!
All of you, hold on a second.
I understand that you
want to see him again,
but I won't allow you
to bring him back here.
You can't kiss his ass and tell
him you're happy to see him again.
You know that.
Until he bows his head and apologizes
for what he did, he can't come back.
Zoro, you big dick!
Hey, I don't know what
your problem is, but...
Shut up!
It doesn't matter what you two were
thinking when you started arguing.
and it doesn't matter who was
wrong or who was right either.
When two men agree to have
a duel with each other,
no matter what the outcome
is, they have to accept it.
I challenge you to a duel!
And after he lost that duel,
he left by his own accord.
You understand, don't you?
He may be an idiot, but this
guy is still our captain.
We're better off without a crew member who
doesn't respect their leader
when things get rough.
A crew with no respect
and a captain that doesn't
demand it are destined
to fall apart quickly.
Listen!
I don't mind if you're
easygoing most of the time,
but right now you've got to man up!
You can't let people walk all over you!
Because if you do that, it's going
to be me who leaves this crew!
You're making this more
complicated than it needs to be!
Don't get me wrong,
it's fine if he joins the crew again,
and it's fine if you want him back.
But,
if he doesn't apologize for what he did,
and pretends like nothing ever
happened between the two of you,
then I won't forgive him
and I won't stand for it.
In other words, we'll leave
the island without him.
Wait, Zoro, I agree that Usopp's
the one at fault, not Luffy.
But we can settle that with him
after he joins up with us again.
So the fact that he left
our crew means nothing
he can come and go as he pleases No but I
Nami I hate to admit it but just this once
at least I have to agree
with what he's saying
If he pulls a pointless
stunt like this on a
whim then how are we
supposed to trust him moving
Forward it's simple if
the first thing that comes
out of Usop's mouth is an
apology then we're good
But if he tries to make some
excuse then he's no longer welcome
We're not just pretending to
be pirates this isn't a game
So long, Usopp.
It was fun.
Well, it lasted.
You're right.
We already went our separate ways before.
There's still a few days until
they finish with the ship.
We can wait that long.
It's all up to him.
Vice Admiral Garp
We have found the Straw
Hat crew's location.
They're on Scrap Island.
They're preparing to depart as we speak.
So we don't have long, sir.
After him, man.
Everyone, get on the ship. Yes, sir.
Vice Admiral Garp After having such a
heartwarming farewell With
Luffy and his friends?
Don't you think that
this is rather awkward?
Tell that to Sengoku,
not me He's the one who got all Pass
and told us we had to come back.
Cocky bastard.
Should have known that I can't catch
my grandson wasn't a good excuse.
Hey, shut your trap, you rookie.
What do you know?
Uh, are you sure you want
to take a nap there, sir?
We're about to go to battle.
It'd be a pain to ride the
headquarters on my bike.
It's fine.
I'll stay out of the way.
Uh, maybe you should go inside.
Or even better, you could help us fight.
I can do it!
I'm joining the crew again!
I'm sure the new ship is done by now.
Everyone must be waiting
for me to come back!
I wasn't procrastinating.
I was waiting for the perfect time.
Not that I'm going to
have a problem anyway.
I've been training day and
night, so I'm ready for anything.
But we are friends, so just to be nice,
I'll try not to make a big
deal about how awesome I am.
Since all of you are crying and
begging on your hands and knees,
I guess I'll make an exception
and come back as first mate.
Oh, first mate, Usopp,
you're the best ever! Yay!
We'll do anything you say
as long as you come back.
Or something like that.
See, I always knew I was a genius.
I may fall down, but I
always get right back up.
After conquering adversity,
everyone will love the brave hero, Usopp,
even more, and we'll all
live happily ever after.
All right, full speed ahead!
We've had some good times,
but this is farewell.
Thanks for having me, Water 7!
Sit still!
The Freaky Family will never die!
When you come back, we'll be
right here waiting for you!
So that's it? We're leaving?
Luffy!
Last call, Straw Hat. Are you sure?
Seems like we're still missing someone.
Nah, it's okay.
We've waited long enough already
and he never bothered to show up
We waited for him all that time,
but he never bothered to come.
So I guess we have our answer?
He'll be fine.
It's not like he quit being a pirate.
It's a big world out there
But I'm sure we'll run into
him again someday even if
he isn't one of us anymore.
Damn it!
Bad news!
The Marines are here!
Ripper!
It's got battleship. Yeah,
I
hear you what's
the deal what
are you doing coming back here?
You said you were gonna leave us alone.
Well, I say a lot of things truth of the
matter is I'm sending you to a watery grave
Wado?!
I know this isn't much consolation.
For what it's worth, I'll
fight you all on my own.
Cannonball, please. Right!
Coming up!
What's he trying to do?
I call this one my...
Peter's Miss!
He just threw that with his bare hands!
I flew faster than any
cannonball I've ever seen,
And he pitched it just like a baseball.
Those used to fly a lot
faster in my younger days.
Listen up.
We got to get out of here right now.
If we don't, he's going to
wreck our brand new ship.
Now bring me a thousand
more on the double.
Yes, sir.
This is bad.
Looks like there's plenty
more where that came from.
The meteor fist shower? Uh-oh.
Those guys are as good as dead.
Just one shot and their
ship is going up in smoke.
Now, I hope you're ready, boys and girls.
Full speed ahead!
Everyone protect the ship
from those cannonballs!
Got it!
Damn it.
Is he really not coming?
What is that idiot doing?
He's here!
Usopp came back after all!
You hear that, guys?
Usopp's right over there!
Are you sure? Uh-huh!
Let me through! Move! Move!
I'm sorry, this is important!
Hey, what are you doing, long-nose?
Shouldn't you be on that boat?
Wait, what the heck's going on?
Why are the Marines here, and
why is Loopy leaving already?
You're really out of the loop, aren't you?
This has got to be a mistake!
Sure, we had our differences, but you
can't really be leaving without me!
They can't they can't
how can they do this?
We're still friends aren't we we've
been fighting side-by-side all this time
You know I was there right
after all that happened
I may have worn that
mask to protect my pride,
but it was still me
Is that it?
The stairs are broken
over there, you know?
Don't hurt yourself!
It's a misunderstanding!
It has to be!
Hey! Look, everyone!
I'm right here! Don't worry!
I made it in time!
I'm coming back to the crew!
I'm not kidding.
Don't leave me here!
Now come, come, come alone!
It's up here!
They'll be here!
That's too late!
Everyone protect the ship!
Hey!
You should be happy!
Your friend Ousup's back!
So how about the weather
we're having today, Chopper?
We should go fishing!
After the cannonballs are gone, of course!
Oh, by the way, I got some great news!
If you guys just turn around
and pick me up right now,
then I'll be happy to
be your vice-captain!
Good deal, huh?
Hey!
Luffy!
Guys!
It's okay!
I know you're nervous about seeing
me again, but we're all buddies here!
Come on!
It's not a big deal!
Luffy, I'm sorry I can't
follow you anymore.
And I'm sorry I was in
pain till the bitter end.
Don't tell me you actually believe that!
I was just kidding!
After all the stuff we've
been through together,
I wouldn't leave the crew over
something silly like that!
Sure, we had a little
disagreement, but we're friends!
And friends can put the
past behind them, right?
Hey, you hear me?
Say something, you guys!
This isn't funny anymore!
I can't hear.
I don't hear anything.
You liar, he's right there!
You're serious, aren't you?
I can't believe this You're really
gonna leave without me, huh?
That's fine.
You've made your decision.
If that's how it is, then I have
only one thing to say to you.
Wherever I go, it's my business.
It has nothing to do with you anymore.
I'm leaving the crew.
This is goodbyes.
I'm too stubborn! I know!
I take back every word I said!
That's more like it.
I know I'm being pathetic.
I know I already said I quit.
But will you let me take it back please
I'm begging you you gotta forgive me!
If I'm not with you there's no point
don't leave me alone I need you guys!
I'll do anything please let me
join the crew just one more time?
Hurry up!
Grab on already!
You better not drop them.
Pretty lame, you two. Pull it together.
All right, the gang's all here.
We're going to get away from these stupid
cannonballs and head to the new world.
Let's go.
You can do it!
Show the Navy who's boss!
Are you kidding?
They're done for!
They're criminals.
Don't cheer so loud.
Come on, Straw Hat!
Don't give up now!
Keep moving!
Go, go, go!
Hang in there, big room!
no way what the heck do they
think they're doing why are they
burling their sails they're not
giving up are they not on your life
i don't know what that fool is up
to but my grandson's no quitter
i'll tell you that hurry up i
said furl the sails yeah he said
you sure about this Franky doesn't seem
very smart to me Hey, stop being an idiot!
Have some faith in your own ship!
Come on, idiot!
Come on, man!
Just a second ago, you were
crying, and now you're...
Nope, never mind, whatever.
Why don't you shut up and help me?
Don't you know?
We can't leave until we
give this ship a name.
A name?
At a time like this?
Of course.
This is our maiden voyage, so there's
no point if we don't do it now.
Whatever it is, it's got
to have Lion in it, right?
Wait, I got it!
I just thought of the perfect name!
The Black Bear, Polar Bear, Lion, Tiger!
That's a horrible name for a ship!
No way!
Then how about the Super
Wolf, Gorilla Bear?
Naming off animals.
Can't you pick one and work from there?
The Squid, Octopus, Chimpanzee!
What happened to the lion?
Uh-huh.
Well, I did have a lion
in mind for the design.
Though the guys at Galilad
didn't seem to get that.
That figurehead's nice, huh? Yeah!
I love sunflowers!
I'm a sunflower, you morons!
Well, don't take it so hard.
You can't expect that everyone is
going to see it for what it is.
But this is the ship the future
king of the pirates will ride.
That's what you were thinking
when you built it, right, Franky?
Damn straight.
The oceans in the new
world may have monsters,
but this is the king of beasts
that will reign over them all.
A splendid sun and dis...
It's not the sun, you moron!
A ship as bright as the sun,
sailing with a shining smile?
as it soars over the
dangers of a thousand seas.
It needs a name to match that feeling.
I told you it's not
the sun ice for brains!
It might not be my place,
but I have a suggestion.
Why don't you call this ship...
The Thousand Sunny!
Ooh, I like it!
Me too, it's super cold!
I was thinking Dandelion, Lion, Dandy,
Unbearable Bear, but this is way better!
Just stop!
I kind of wanted Big Boss Lionel, but
Thousand Sunny is pretty good, too.
I was going to suggest
Creature of Darkness.
I like Monsieur Sunflower, Purcell.
Have all of you lost your minds?
A ship to sail a thousand
seas with a sunny smile.
It's perfect, don't you think?
Don't get too excited, you guys.
That was just a warm-up.
I've got a name that's
gonna knock your socks off.
This ship will now be known as...
Hello, guys, Pop's idea just fine.
Let's go with that and get this ship done.
Sounds good.
A thousandth sunny it is.
I agree!
Nice to meet you, Sunny!
Thought we'd have a harder time agreeing
on this, but I guess it worked out fine.
So it did.
Hey, Franky, stop pouting and get moving.
Use this secret weapon of yours
so we can get out of here.
Better make it fast, too.
The Navy's gonna catch up any second.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Take one last look at Water 7,
because it's gonna be out
of sight before you know it.
I'm warning you, once we start
moving, we'll really be moving.
Okay, got it. One sec.
Grandpa!
Oh, and if you're there, Colby, and...
The other guy!
It was nice to see you again!
You forgot my name again, didn't you?
What are you yapping about, Luffy?
I got plenty more cannonballs.
Meteor... Fish!
Give it off!
I don't know what's going to
happen, but we're going to get away.
Well, I hope to see
you guys again someday.
Wow, Loopy, that was super cool.
You little turd, you show your
grandpa some respect, you hear me?
How dare you?
I know he's annoying you
like that, but calm down.
Thanks for helping us
name the ship Ice Pops.
You're awesome.
And thanks to everybody else, too.
Bye, Monster Granny.
Bye, Galley-La.
We had a great time.
I think he's saying something.
I can't hear a darn thing.
It seems that pirates can't even go out
to sea without causing a giant ruckus.
There we go.
Combining the power of our air can
with the durability of the Atomwood,
I've made an emergency
acceleration device.
I'll pound some manners into you.
Luffy, run away!
He's serious this time!
Breaking!
There it goes!
We're all gonna die!
Who did first?
Did their ship take off and fly away?
Not bad, kiddo.
I can't believe it.
I never thought I'd feel
this again, but here I am.
Mary.
It eats up three barrels of cola,
but it can fly for a whole kilometer.
I'm not trying to brag
here, but simply put,
anything that Going Mary could
do, this ship can do better.
And it's got tricks of its own.
But even if it's all new!
I hope the brave spirit of the
Mary can live on in this sudden?
If anything breaks, I'll
fix it up as good as new.
From weapons to furniture, I
know this ship up and down.
It may be my masterpiece,
but it's all yours now.
I'll be damned!
They got away after all.
That's my grandson for you.
It's kind of a shame I wish the
little guy had stayed with us.
Yeah, I'm gonna miss him,
but wherever he goes he still
wants to come to Elbeth someday.
And we'll be there waiting when he does.
Sounds like fun.
We got a couple hundred years left on
us, so we can afford to be patient.
Nothing like a job well done.
Yeah, you said it.
Let's see what they need at the workshop.
We've still got repair work to do, too.
Bring it on.
Better head back to the station.
Gonna be business as usual soon.
Huh? Let's see.
How did Big Bro do this stuff? Beats me.
Yeah, this is bad.
I always just did what he told me to do.
Guess we're going to starve to death, huh?
Iceberg!
I had a feeling something like this
would happen to you, Riff Reef.
What?
Did you come here just to make fun of us?
No, I came to offer you a job.
If you need work, then you should
stop by the Galley-La offices.
Do you really mean it, Iceberg?
Icebro? No! Bigbro!
Our new Bigbro!
Stop that.
Commodore Smoker, excellent work Huh, you
said that pirate had a 50 million bounty?
Yes, sir.
Pathetic, the Navy standards
are dropping these days!
One disappointment after another.
Excuse me, Smoker.
It's in Tashigi.
Did you see the Straw Hats wanted posters?
They all have bounties Who do
you think you're talking to?
Oh, you're not Smoker, oops
Wear your glasses, stupid.
Unbelievable!
Nico, Robin, what in the world is
Miss Allsunday doing on Luffy's crew?
I knew there was something mysterious about
that woman, but this is quite the shock.
If this news reaches Princess Vivi,
I can only imagine how
disheartened she would be.
Oh, don't worry.
I already heard about that.
It's no big deal, though.
It's not a big deal!
I thought you of all
people would be shocked!
Even when you're as
close to Luffy as I was,
you can never quite
tell what he's thinking.
Whether I understand his reasoning or not,
I still believe in everything he does.
Because I know that he's going to
be king of the pirates one day.
The best we can do is
respect his decisions.
How forgiving.
You've turned into such a fine
young lady, Princess Vivi.
Hey, it's nothing to cry about. Out.
The navy will always be the navy and
as long as we're part of the military
there's a limit to what we can
accomplish on our own in other words
what we need is a higher rank after
that incident at Enies Lobby pirates
from all over the world will be
looking up to Straw Hat and his crew
i see
i'm putting my pride on the line here i
swear i will crush them in the new world
All right, guys!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Then everybody raise a glass for the
return of our old friends Robin and Usopp,
as well as our new crew member, Franky?
and the best ship ever,
the Thousand Money!
Let's hear it for our crew!
Cheers!
Let's go!
Next stop, Fishman Island!
Yeah!